whmnet.org 2016-03-16

# World Heritage Memory Net - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  

The _World Heritage Memory Net_ understands your concerns about privacy. We are committed to protecting the integrity and security of your personal information. To that end, this Privacy Policy presented here is to provide you with notice of what information we collect on this Web site ("Site") and how such information may be used. This Privacy Policy is subject to the ["Terms of Use"](http://chen2.simmons.edu/whm3/about/?content=term_use) posted on this Site. Please review these statements from time to time, as they are subject to change without notice.

**INFORMATION ON YOU AND HOW OUR SITE MAKES USE OF IT**

As a general policy, registration is required to browse the Site. Such information may include contact information (such as your name and e-mail address) and geographic information. In addition to this, we also collect aggregated information (such as the number of users who log on to the Site on a daily basis). The personal information you submit to us will only be used by us to carry out your requests and respond to your inquiries. It may also be used for internal research purposes, which may include contacting you (by e-mail or by mail) about features of the Site. Some data will be used to determine research questions related to the behavior of users of digital libraries, thus we greatly appreciate receiving your most complete and accurate user information when you first register with us. We do not provide your personal information to any third parties whatsoever.

Please note that if you voluntarily disclose personal information on our Registration, that information can also possibly be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. We may aggregate information which does not personally identify you to create statistical data. Such information can include the type of browsers being used (e.g. Internet Explorer, Firefox), the operating system you are using (e.g. Windows XP, Mac OS), and the number of users that visit a specific page on the Site and the character and duration of such visits. This aggregated information will be used to help analyze site traffic and improve our services. We may also use such aggregated information to describe the Site's use statistics to potential partners or other third parties. At no point, however, will the aggregated information identify you. We reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or aggregated information if required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary in order to (a) conform with the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served on _World Heritage Memory Net_ ; (b) to protect or defend the legal rights or property of _World Heritage Memory Net_ , the Site, or its users; or (c) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of the Site's users or the general public. 

You may remove your name from our list by contacting us at:

_World Heritage Memory Net  
_c/o Dr. Ching-chih Chen  
President, [Global Connection and Collaboration](http://globalcc.org/)  
1400 Commonwealth Avenue  
Newton, Massachusetts 02465[  
](mailto:ccc@globalcc.org)617-413-3126   
Email: [ccc@globalcc.org](mailto:ccc@globalcc.org)

**Links** \- Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not maintained by _World Heritage Memory Net_. We provide these links as a convenience only, and have not reviewed in depth all of the sites linked to the _WHMNet_ Site. Therefore, a link does not imply endorsement of, sponsorship of, or affiliation with the linked site by _World Heritage Memory Net_. Please review their privacy policy statement before submitting any personal information to such sites.

**Security Procedures** \- No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, _World Heritage Memory Net_ cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information. 

**Contact Us** \- If you have any questions about this privacy policy or any matter pertaining to the use of your personal information on this site, or if you would like to review or change the information you have provided to us, please contact us as mentioned above. 

**Consent** \- By your use of our Site, you consent to the use of your personal information as expressed in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time, with any such change in the policy effective immediately on the posting of the revised policy on this site.
